- You know what would be nice?
- What's that?
(Sheldon:)As a symbolic gesture to all the bullies
who've tormented us for years...
(Sheldon:)...we open our home to Jimmy,
and once he's asleep, we kill him.
(Sheldon:)I said it would be nice.
I didn't say we should do it.
Oh. I feel just like Mother Teresa.
(Penny:)Except for the virgin part.
That ship sailed a long time ago.
(Bernadette:)I think Mother Teresa
would've washed the clothes first.
(Penny:)Yeah, well, I bet her laundry room
wasn't down five flights of stairs.
(Penny:)You know, giving really
is better than receiving.
Oh. I used to think it was such a cliché,
but it seems to be the...
Ah! Look at these cute jeans
someone just threw away.
(Bernadette:)Donated.
(Penny:)Yes, to a poor waitress
who loves a boot-cut.